When people are lying to somebody else,
I mean, knowingly lying,
the body language that matters the most is not eye contact.
That's what people focus that they think eye contact
is the most important signal.
It's not because people learn very different things
in different households and cultures,
personality differences that change how people
choose to make eye contact in different situations.
What matters is the asyncrany
between the emotions conveyed with the words
and the emotions conveyed with the body language.
So if you're telling a happy story,
but you do not look happy,
your body language doesn't look happy,
you don't come across as authentic.